Guide to The Polytechnic Reporter RG.025
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
The Polytechnic Reporter
1914-2014
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.025
9 Linear Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
- Series I: Loose newspapers
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 June 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 November 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1914 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 January 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 January 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 18 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 May 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 November 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1915 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 April 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 April 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 May 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 November 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1916 December 21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 November 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1917 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 December 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1918 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 April 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1919 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 February 27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1920 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 January 12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 9 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 16 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 9 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 16 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 April 20 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 19 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 October 26 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 November 30 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1921 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 January 11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 April 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 April 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 May 10 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 September 27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 22 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 November 29 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 December 13 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1922 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 January 5 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 7 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 21 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 7 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 March 28 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 April 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 April 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 October 31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 21 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 November 28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 December 12 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1923 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 January 9 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 19 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 April 30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 May 8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 October 29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 19 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 November 26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 December 3 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1924 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 4 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 18 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 February 26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 4 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 March 25 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Vol. 3, No. 1-29 (duplicates), 1915-1916 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Vol. 5, No. 1-28 (duplicates), 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 September 30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 7 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 15 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 October 28 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 5 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 11 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 16 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1925 December 23 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 January 14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 February 25 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 10 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 April 21 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 April 28 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 May 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 May 12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 September 23 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 14 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 20 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 October 27 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 4 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 17 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 December 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)